evenko.ca 2015-05-16

# Privacy Policy | evenko

**Introduction and Acceptance**

Welcome to the evenko website located at [http://evenko.ca](http://evenko.ca/) (the “Website”) which includes all subdomains present and future, the Ticketing System located at distinct subdomains of <https://wroom.centrebell.ca/> or [https://ind.eventshopper.com](https://ind.eventshopper.com/) (when the Ticketing System is accessed through a mobile device), and / or the Android or iOS evenko mobile application (the “App”). The Website, Ticketing System and App are collectively referred to as the “Services”. We hope you enjoy your visit and / or use of the Services. By visiting the Website and / or using the Services, you agree to be bound by the terms of the present Privacy Policy (the “Policy”).

evenko is owned and operated by L’Aréna des Canadiens Inc., a duly incorporated company in the province of Québec, Canada. Where the present Policy refers to “evenko”, it may refer to evenko or L’Aréna des Canadiens Inc. or both, depending on the context.

The Policy was last modified on October 23, 2013. evenko reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to modify or replace any of the Policy. Any changes to the Policy can be found at this URL. It is your responsibility to check the Policy periodically for changes. Your use of the Services following the posting of any changes to the Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.

The Policy should be read in conjunction with the [Terms of Use](http://www.evenko.ca/en/show/page/terms_and_conditions), as both these documents govern your use of the Services. Where you use the Ticketing System through the Services, you are also bound by the [Purchase Agreement for Tickets](http://www.evenko.ca/en/show/page/purchase_agreement).

If you have any questions about the Policy, please [**contact us here**](http://www.evenko.ca/en/show/contact_us), or:

**evenko Legal Services**

c/o L’Aréna des Canadiens Inc.

1275 rue Saint-Antoine Ouest

Montréal (Québec) H3C 5L2

**General Statement of Privacy and Protection of Personal Information**

evenko takes your privacy and security of personal information very seriously. We have provided a secure environment and this strict Policy that describes the limited ways the information is used and the limited access to such information.

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other information gathered by evenko when you are using or accessing the Services. This Policy also covers evenko’s treatment of any Personal Information that evenko may share with its business partners or other third parties under very limited circumstances.

This Policy does not apply to the general practices and treatment of information by third parties that evenko does not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites or services that you elect to access through the Services (“Third Party Services”), or to individuals that evenko does not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

Without limiting the generality of the preceding paragraph, evenko may use third-party ticket vendors (“Ticket Vendors”) for certain events, such as Admission and TicketPro, and this Policy does not cover information submitted to these Ticket Vendors that evenko does not control. However, these Ticket Vendors may transfer to evenko certain Personal Information such as your email address, but only if you consent to such sharing by the Ticket Vendor at their website or through the use of their services. Furthermore, in the event of a cancellation, postponement, or other significant change to an event for which you purchased tickets through a Ticket Vendor, evenko may request your full contact information in order to inform you of the change in the event information. In such a case, we will not use this Personal Information for any other purpose.

Finally, this Policy does not cover any Personal Information you send to evenko via any non-secured mode of communications such as email, instant messenger or Twitter, as communications via these methods may be subject to interception, loss, or alteration. We encourage you to carefully examine what Personal Information you send to evenko via these methods.

**No Collection of Personal Information**

evenko does not, as a matter of course, gather any of your Personal Information while you are using the Services, unless you are asked to provide such information, for example by signing up to the mailing list. Where you have provided such information, it will only be used for the stated purpose.

Personal Information may be entered into the Website or App when you wish to connect to a third party service integrated into the Website or App, such as Facebook or Twitter (the “Integrated Third Party Services”) but this information is not in any way collected or stored by evenko, and it is only used for the stated purpose, to sign in to the Integrated Third Party Service.

**Collection of Personal Information through the Ticketing System**

When you use the Ticketing System to purchase tickets, evenko collects the following Personal Information: name, email address, credit card information, and billing information including address and phone number. This information is only used for the following purposes: credit card processing; contacting you in the event of a cancellation, postponement, or other significant change to an event; and advertising or marketing purposes, but only upon your consent.

**Security of Information**

We use only industry best practices in keeping any data collected secure. This includes the HTTPS / SSL / TLS (Secure Socket Layer) protocol for all ticket-purchasing transactions and for authentication and data transfer to Integrated Third-Party Services. In addition, evenko uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Services, and these vendors have been selected for their high standards of security.

**Limited Gathering of Information for Statistical and Security Purposes**

evenko automatically collects certain information using a third-party analytics program, [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), to help us understand how our users use the Services, but none of this information identifies you personally. For example, each time you visit the Website or otherwise use the Services, we automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access times, the web page from which you came, and the web page(s) you access (as applicable). We use this information only to better understand your needs and the needs of the Services users in the aggregate. evenko also makes use of information gathered for statistical purposes to keep track of the number of visits to the Website and which pages on the Website with a view to introducing improvements.

Your IP address and other relevant information may be used in order to trace any fraudulent or criminal activity, or any activity in violation of the Terms of Service.

**Non-disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**

Except as provided in the next paragraphs, evenko does not divulge any Personal Information gathered via the Services to third parties. Moreover, evenko does not sell any information regarding its users to third parties. Only the employees, representatives, subcontractors, or officers of evenko are responsible for the management and development of the Services, and only these individuals have access to the information collected there. These employees, representatives, subcontractors, or officers all have been instructed to comply with the Policy.

Notwithstanding anything in the Policy to the contrary, we may share any information we have collected about you or that you have submitted: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or demands; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding situations that involve abuse of the Services infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of the Website infrastructure or the Services generally); (4) to a parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with evenko (in which case we will require such entities to honour this Policy); (5) if evenko is acquired by or merged with another entity (in which case we will require such entity to assume our obligations under this Policy, or inform you that you are covered by a new privacy policy); (6) when you explicitly consent to the providing of such information to third parties, such as our business partners, when it will only be used for the stated purpose.

In addition, evenko uses certain Integrated Third Party Services to augment the Services. Personal Information is transferred from evenko to the operators of these Integrated Third Party Services, but only to the extent required in order for them to function properly, and only upon your express submission of such information.

Finally, evenko may transfer your email address to Facebook, but only for the purpose of creating a [Facebook Custom Audience](https://www.facebook.com/help/341425252616329), in order to serve advertisements on Facebook that may be of interest to you. Please see the “Advertisements” section further in this Policy for more information.

**Removal from Mailing List and Deletion of Personal Information**

You may unsubscribe from evenko’s mailing list at any time, by following the link at the bottom of all evenko emails or by visiting our **[Unsubscribe Page](http://evenko.us3.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=bc6b4b00ca21a02c0dd9820a0&id=380cc078f5)**. Note that unsubscribing from the mailing list in this manner may not necessarily delete all your Personal Information from evenko databases. If you wish to ensure that all Personal Information is removed from our databases, please [contact us](http://www.evenko.ca/en/show/contact_us). 

**Tracking Technology ("Cookies")**

evenko uses tracking technology (“cookies”) on the Website and by using the Services you agree to their use. Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive when you visit a web site, in order to track use of the site and to improve the user experience by storing certain data on your computer. The Website uses “session cookies,” which improve your user experience by storing certain information from your current visit on your computer.

Your browser can be set to refuse cookies or delete them after they have been stored. Please note that deleting or refusing these cookies may reduce your user experience for the Services by requiring you to re-enter certain information, such as regional preference. Furthermore, most session cookies used by evenko will expire after a brief period of time or upon closing your browsing session.

The Ticketing System uses certain session cookies such as waiting room position, the event requested, and the number of requests, but none of these cookies can identify you personally. Please note that deleting or refusing these session cookies may hamper your ability to properly purchase tickets through the Ticketing System, and evenko disclaims all responsibility for any damages, pecuniary or non-pecuniary, resulting from your inability to purchase tickets if you delete or refuse such cookies.

In addition to the evenko session cookies on the Website and the Ticketing System, the Website also uses cookies from third parties including [Doubleclick](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/) (a subsidiary of Google, for the serving of advertisements on the Website), and [AddThis](http://www.addthis.com/) (for sharing of content via social media). There are also cookies used by YouTube, Facebook, and Twitter for various widgets and integration of content. The use of these third-party cookies is governed by their respective owners and evenko has no control over them and disclaims any responsibility for their use. These cookies can be refused or deleted by your browser at any time, though deleting them may reduce or inhibit your use of certain third-party functionalities integrated into the Services.

**Advertisements**

evenko currently uses [Google AdWords](https://adwords.google.com/) and by using the Services you consent to this use. Specifically, evenko uses the remarketing features of interest-based advertising of Google AdWords that delivers you advertisements that will be of particular interest to you, based on your browsing history at the Website. These advertisements will appear on third-party websites around the web. Google uses specific cookies to allow them to serve these ads around the web that will be of interest to you.

You may prevent this type of advertising by deleting the appropriate Google cookie through your browser, though this may not be permanent. For a more permanent solution, you may opt out of such Google advertising at any time by visiting your [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

evenko may use your email address when creating [Facebook Custom Audience](https://www.facebook.com/help/341425252616329)s. We may submit your email address to Facebook in order to determine if you are a registered user of Facebook and if that is the case to display advertisements to you on Facebook that will be of interest to you. Facebook will not share that information with third parties, will maintain the strict confidentiality of the Custom Audience, and will immediately delete the data once it is determined if you are a registered Facebook user or not. If you do not want to receive such Facebook advertisements, please [contact us](http://www.evenko.ca/en/show/contact_us).

evenko reserves the right to use additional retargeting or other ad services in the future. In such a case, evenko will update this section of the Policy with further details.

**Risks Associated with the Internet**

Despite evenko's efforts to ensure third parties will not access or obtain your Personal Information through your use of the Services, complete confidentiality and security cannot currently be guaranteed on the Internet. Communication via the Internet is subject to interception, loss, or alteration. You acknowledge and agree that evenko cannot be held responsible for damages resulting from the transmission of confidential information or Personal Information over the Internet and that such communications are at your own risk.

**Limitation of Liability**

evenko, and / or its respective officers, directors, owners, officials, partners, partnerships, principals, employees, affiliates and other related entities, servants, agents, representatives, successors and assigns, will not be held liable for any damages resulting from the misuse of any information collected via the Third Party Services or by any third party, or any misuse of any information collected through the Website not in violation of the Policy.

© L’Aréna des Canadiens Inc. 2013
